let quiz=[
    {
      question: "The COMMON WEALTH GAMES 2002 were held in :",
      option: [
           "Toranto",
           "Manchester",
           "Tokyo",
           "Canberra",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "The C.K. Nayudu Trophy is related to the sport of :",
      option: [
           "Cricket",
           "Hockey",
           "Football",
           "Chess",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "When Leander Paes won the mixed doubles at the US Open in the year 2008, who of the following was his partner :",
      option: [
           "Ana Ivanovic",
           "Cara Black",
           "Dinara Safina",
           "Jelena Jankovic",
      ],
       answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "_______ on December 27, 2009, won the 38th senior National men's handball championship, dethroning Services in the finalin kolkata : ",
      option: [
           "Railways",
           "State Bank of India",
           "Jharkhand",
           "Chhattisgarh",
      ],
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Among the following, which one is not a football club :",
      option: [
           "Arsenal",
           "Aston Villa",
           "Chelesa",
           "Monte Carlo",
      ],
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "How many times did Geet Sethi win the LBSF World Billiards title :",
      option: [
           "2",
           "3",
           "4",
           "5",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "In the 2010 Commonwealth Games being Hosted by New Delhi, which two new disciplines will be added :",
      option: [
           "Billiards and Kabaddi",
           "Tennia and Archery",
           "Basketball and Volleyball",
           "Tennis and Billiards",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "In which year did Milkha Singh win the first National title in the 400m race :",
      option: [
           "1955",
           "1956",
           "1957",
           "1970",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Jaspal Rana is the name associated with which of the following games :",
      option: [
           "Boxing",
           "Shooting",
           "Archery",
           "Weight Lifting",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Merdeka Cup is associated with :",
      option: [
           "Cricket",
           "Football",
           "Chess",
           "Hockey",
      ],
      answer: 2 ,
    },
    ]   